  
 //alert('i am ok')

    var jsonResponse = [
    //{
    //             "subjectId":"1",
    //             "id":"1",
    //             "questionText": "Which is valid javascript statement?",
    //             "options":[
    //                 {"text":"console.log('Hello...')","value":"1"},
    //                 {"text":"console.log('Hello...'","value":"2"},
    //                 {"text":"console.log 'Hello...')","value":"3"},
    //                 {"text":"console.log 'Hello...'","value":"4"}
    //             ],
    //             "answers":["1"],
    //             "answerType":"Radio"
            
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"2",
    //         "questionText": "Which are falsy values?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"Empty string","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"Nunullll","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"undefined","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"function","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1","2","3"],
    //         "answerType":"Checkbox"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"3",
    //         "questionText": "Object literal one of the type in javascript?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"Data","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"Function","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"Operator","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"Array","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"4",
    //         "questionText": "Each property can defined by which symble?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"Curly braces","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"Coma","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"Colon","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"Semicolon","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"5",
    //         "questionText": "If we declared 14.95 as variable which function is needed?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"parseFloat()","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"parseInt()","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"prompt()","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"alert()","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"6",
    //         "questionText": "n its indicate new line but its does not work in which javascript object?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"Document.write()","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"Alert()","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"Prompt()","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"parseInt()","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1","2","3","4"],
    //         "answerType":"Checkbox"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"7",
    //         "questionText": "If we put 'My dog is named Fred' as string literal than its return to",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"My dog is named fred","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"My dog is named “Fred","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"‘My dog is named’ Fred","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"My dog is named Fred","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["2"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"8",
    //         "questionText": "C-style block-level scoping is not supported in Java script",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"False","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"True","value":"2"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["2"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"9",
    //         "questionText": "JavaScript is an object oriented language?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"True","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"False","value":"2"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //         },
    //         {
    //         "subjectId":"1",
    //         "id":"10",
    //         "questionText": "Which of the following is used to capture all click events in a window?",
    //         "options":[
    //             {"text":"window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK)","value":"1"},
    //             {"text":"window.routeEvents(Event.CLICK );","value":"2"},
    //             {"text":"window.handleEvents (Event.CLICK)","value":"3"},
    //             {"text":"window.raiseEvents(Event.CLICK )","value":"4"}
    //         ],
    //         "answers":["1"],
    //         "answerType":"Radio"
    
    //          },
            {
            "subjectId":"3",
            "id":"11",
            "questionText": "Which is the correct JavaScript syntax for 'for/in' loop?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"for(variable in object){statement}","value":"1"},
                {"text":"for(object in variable){statement}","value":"2"},
                {"text":"forin(object in variable){statement}","value":"3"},
                {"text":"forin(variable; test; increment){statement}","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["1"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"3",
            "id":"12",
            "questionText": "which Property Name are valid in javascript ?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"AlinkColor","value":"1"},
                {"text":"LinkObject","value":"2"},
                {"text":"Cookie","value":"3"},
                {"text":"Domain","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["1","2","4"],
            "answerType":"Checkbox"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"3",
            "id":"13",
            "questionText": "Which of the following value of Boolean literal in JavaScript is/are correct?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"yes/no","value":"1"},
                {"text":"1/0","value":"2"},
                {"text":"True/False","value":"3"},
                {"text":"y/n","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["2","3"],
            "answerType":"Checkbox"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"3",
            "id":"14",
            "questionText": "A function or variable name in JavaScript begins with __?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"an ASCII letter","value":"1"},
                {"text":"a dollar sign","value":"2"},
                {"text":"an ASCII letter or underscore","value":"3"},
                {"text":"an ASCII letter, dollar sign or underscore","value":"4"},
                {"text":"an ASCII letter or dollar sign","value":"5"}
            ],
            "answers":["4"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"2",
            "id":"15",
            "questionText": "'^' is ______ oparator.?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"bitwise xor","value":"1"},
                {"text":"bitwise or","value":"2"},
                {"text":"bitwise not","value":"3"}
            ],
            "answers":["1"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"2",
            "id":"16",
            "questionText": "Compound data are made up of A)_____s and B)_____s in JavaScript ?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"array,object","value":"1"},
                {"text":"object,array","value":"2"},
                {"text":"fanction","value":"3"},
                {"text":"undifined","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["1","2"],
            "answerType":"Checkbox"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"2",
            "id":"17",
            "questionText": "prompt() is not an input function in JavaScript?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"True","value":"1"},
                {"text":"False","value":"2"}
            ],
            "answers":["2"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"2",
            "id":"18",
            "questionText": "How would you use a timer with a function called rearrange()?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"tmr=setTimeout('rearrange()',1)","value":"1"},
                {"text":"tmr=Timer(1,'rearrange()')","value":"2"},
                {"text":"tmr=Timer(1,'rearrange()',1)","value":"3"},
                {"text":"tmr=setTimeout(1,'rearrange()')","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["1"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"2",
            "id":"19",
            "questionText": "Which of the following is/are not the Math function(s)?",
            "options":[
                {"text":"maxmax()","value":"1"},
                {"text":"average()","value":"2"},
                {"text":"ceil()","value":"3"},
                {"text":"random()","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["2"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            },
            {
            "subjectId":"2",
            "id":"20",
            "questionText": "Which of the following is/are the string properties",
            "options":[
                {"text":"length","value":"1"},
                {"text":"toLowerCase","value":"2"},
                {"text":"indexOf","value":"3"},
                {"text":"valueOf","value":"4"}
            ],
            "answers":["1"],
            "answerType":"Radio"
    
            }

];

//================================================

//real question insert into database this formate followed must

    // function questionsInsert() {
    //     var jsonResponse = {
    //             "subjectId":"1",
    //             "id":"1",
    //             "questionText": "Which is valid javascript statement?",
    //             "options":[
    //                 {"text":"mohib","value":"rahman"},
    //                 {"text":"rony","value":"ahmed"},
    //                 {"text":"akash","value":"khan"},
    //                 {"text":"kiron","value":"ahmed"}
    //             ],
    //             "answers":["Your"],
    //             "answerType":"my"    
    //     };


    // var questionsFormLocalstorage=localStorage.getItem("questions");
    // var dataParse=JSON.parse(questionsFormLocalstorage);
    // var newData=dataParse.push(jsonResponse);
    // localStorage.setItem("questions",JSON.stringify(dataParse));
    // }

//==============================================


//after solution database create

    // var questions = [{
    //     "answerStatus": false
    //     "answerType": "Radio"
    //     "answers": ["1"]
    //     "id": "1"
    //     "options": [
    //     {"text": "console.log('Hello...')", "value": "1"}, {"text":"console.log('Hello...'", value: "2"},…]
    //     "questionText": "Which is valid javascript statement?"
    //     "review": true
    //     "reviewTime": 113000
    //     "score": 5
    //     "selected": []
    //     "subjectId": "1"
    //     "viewTime": "01:53"
    // }];